# NARSINHA SHYAMRAO KULKARNI () Featured

Technology Analyst seeking roles in Application Programming, Software Development, Requirement Gathering, Project Management, Business Analysis, Program Management, User Stories, Java, Maven, Hibernate, Spring boot, JSP, JUnit, Apache Tomcat, JEE, Rest, Eclipse



Current Designation: Technology Analyst Total Experience: 5 Year(s) 3 Month(s)

Current Company: Infosys Limited Notice Period: 2 Months

Current Location: Pune Highest Degree: MCA [Computers]

Pref. Location: Ahmedabad, Mumbai, Pune

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Team Lead/Tech Lead, Software Development, Requirement Gathering, Project Management, Business

Analysis, User Stories, Java, Maven, Hibernate, JSP, JUnit, Apache Tomcat, JEE, Rest, Spring

Boot, angular 8, mockito, Microservices

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

### **Summary**

Result-oriented Professional with over 5 years of experience in Application Programming, Software Development, Requirement Gathering, Project Management, Business Analysis, Program Management, User Stories, Java, Maven, Hibernate, Spring Mvc, JSP, JUnit, Apache Tomcat, JEE, Rest, Eclipse

## **Work Experience**

Infosys Limited as Technology Analyst

Mar 2019 to Till Date

Works as Full stack developer with knowledge of java, spring boot, hibernate, junit (mockito) and angular8, protractor.

Softenger as Java Developer

Jan 2018 to Mar 2019

Works as Sr. java developer with knowledge of core java, spring mvc, hibernate, micro services and angularjs

RSL Pvt Ltd as Software Engineer

Oct 2015 to Jan 2018

Worked as Jr. java developer with knowledge of core java, advance java and mysql

#### **Education**

UG: BCS (Computers) from SRTMU, Nanded in 2012

PG: MCA (Computers) from savitribai phule university, pune in 2015

#### IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience	
Java, Spring, Hibernate	8	2021	5 Year(s) 2 Month(s)	
Angular Js, Angular8	8	2021	2 Year(s) 2 Month(s)	
JavaScript, D3JS				
Highchart, HTML, CSS, Protractor, Junit				
Eclipse, Visual Studio Code				
MySQL				
MAVEN				
Apache Tomcat				
Windows, Linux.				
Mockito				
Protractor				

### Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Proficient			
Hindi	Proficient			
Marathi	Expert			

# **Projects**

Project Title: Information Repository Inventory(IRI)

Client: Infosys

Nature of Employment: Full Time
Project Location: Pune
Role: Sr. Programmer

Duration: Oct 2019 - Till Date
Onsite / Offsite: Offsite
Team Size: 6

Skill Used: Spring Boot, angular8, Protractor, Mockito,

Project Details: It is an web application, Manage and validate of a firm information with the consolidated and up to date dashboard views. It contains repositories like share point, share dive and system. Repository ownership validation allows to accept or decline ownership of information repositories. Contains Campaign and Repository ownership validation modules.

Project Title: Uni-connect Web UI

Client: Java Developer - SOFTENGER INDIA

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: May 2018 - Feb 2019

Project Location: Pune Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Team Size: 7

Project Details: Uniconnect is a database integration tool which support multiple database as a single platform. Uniconnect Web Ui is a web application help to create multi node clusters by user interface.

#### **Affirmative Action**

#### **Work Authorization**

Physically Challenged: No Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time